epsbooks.com 2009-09-12

# Customer Service » Privacy Policy

Last updated September 28, 2006.

We are concerned about your right to privacy while accessing and using this Web site. Please take the opportunity to review our Privacy Policy.

**Educators Publishing Service** has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.epsbooks.com.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use the user's IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Cookies**  
Our site uses cookies to keep track of user sessions on our site. We also use cookies to collect anonymous traffic data.

**Registration Forms**  
Our site's registration forms requires users to give us contact information (such as name, e-mail, and postal address), unique identifiers (such as e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

**Order Form**  
Our site's order form requires users to give us contact information (such as name, e-mail, and postal address), financial information (such as purchase order account or credit card number), unique identifiers (such as e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

**Our Use of Personal Data  
** The personal data we obtain from customers via this Web site is used in the following ways:

| • |  | Contact information from the order form is used to ship purchases from Educators Publishing Service.  
---|---|---|---  
• |  | Financial information from the order form is used to bill the customer for products and services.  
• |  | Unique identifiers (such as e-mail addresses) are collected on the registration and order forms to verify the user's identity, for use as account numbers in our record system, and for other purposes.  
• |  | Demographic and profile data collected at our site is used for internal analysis.  
• |  | Contact information from the registration and order forms may be used to send promotional material from Educators Publishing Service to customer mailing addresses. To opt out of receiving promotional materials at their postal mailing address, customers may submit an EPS postal mail opt out request.  
• |  | User e-mail addresses from the registration and order forms may be used to send targeted e-mail from our company. To opt out of receiving promotional materials at their e-mail address, customers may submit an EPS e-mail opt out request.  
  
**Sharing of Personal Data with Third Parties  
** We may exchange customer names and mailing addresses with carefully selected companies that offer educational products that might interest our customers. To opt out of receiving third-party promotional materials at their postal mailing address, customers may submit an EPS postal mail opt out request.

Educators Publishing Service **will not** share customer e-mail addresses or telephone numbers with third-party companies.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Educators Publishing Service **** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. A secure server is used to encrypt credit card information.

**Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives customers only the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send e-mail to [ feedback@epsbooks.com](mailto:feedback@epsbooks.com).
  2. You can call the following telephone number: 800.225.5750 (toll-free).

**Contacting the Web site** **  
** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can e-mail [feedback@epsbooks.com](mailto:feedback@epsbooks.com).
